quiz = {
    1 : {
        "category" : "Very Easy",
        "question" : "What is the first name of Iron Man?",
        "option1" : "Anthon",
        "option2" : "Jhon",
        "option3" : "Jhony",
        "answer" : "Tony"
    },
    2 : {
        "category" : "Very Easy",
        "question" : "Who is called the god of thunder?",
        "option1" : "Jane Foster",
        "option2" : "Black Widow",
        "option3" : "Iron Man",
        "answer" : "Thor"
    },
    3 : {
        "category" : "Very Easy",
        "question" : "Which Avenger always carries a shield of Vibranium?",
        "option1" : "Falcon",
        "option2" : "Winter Soldier",
        "option3" : "Peggy Carter",
        "answer" : "Captain America"
    },
    4 : {
        "category" : "Very Easy",
        "question" : "Which avenger is a green giant with a bad temper?",
        "option1" : "Ant-Man",
        "option2" : "Scarlet Witch",
        "option3" : "Hawkeye",
        "answer" : "Hulk"
    },
    5 : {
        "category" : "Very Easy",
        "question" : "Which avenger can change it's size?",
        "option1" : "Hulk",
        "option2" : "Thor",
        "option3" : "Black Panter",
        "answer" : "Ant-Man"
    },
    6 : {
        "category" : "Very Easy",
        "question" : "Which Avenger has the mind stone?",
        "option1" : "Scarlet Witch",
        "option2" : "Captain America",
        "option3" : "Falcon",
        "answer" : "Vision"
    },
    7 : {
        "category" : "Easy",
        "question" : "What is the name of Captain Marvel?",
        "option1" : "Steve Rogers",
        "option2" : "Mar-Vell",
        "option3" : "Miss Marvel",
        "answer" : "Carol Danvers"
    },
    8 : {
        "category" : "Easy",
        "question" : "What is the name of Spider-Man?",
        "option1" : "Steven Strange",
        "option2" : "Tony Stark",
        "option3" : "Bruce Banner",
        "answer" : "Peter Parker"
    },
    9 : {
        "category" : "Easy",
        "question" : "Which Avenger use a suit of Vibranium?",
        "option1" : "Ant-Man",
        "option2" : "War Machine",
        "option3" : "Iron Man",
        "answer" : "Black Panter"
    },
    10 : {
        "category" : "Easy",
        "question" : "Doctor Strange is ...?",
        "option1" : "some Wizard",
        "option2" : "Scarlet Witch",
        "option3" : "Baron Mordo",
        "answer" : "The Sorcerer Supreme"
    },
    11 : {
        "category" : "Easy",
        "question" : "What is the AI in the Iron Man suit called?",
        "option1" : "JENNY",
        "option2" : "SUNDAY",
        "option3" : "VISION",
        "answer" : "JARVIS"
    },
    12 : {
        "category" : "Easy",
        "question" : "What is the name of Thor's hammer?",
        "option1" : "Vanir",
        "option2" : "Aesir",
        "option3" : "Norn",
        "answer" : "Mjölnir"
    },
    13 : {
        "category" : "Medium",
        "question" : "Who's the leader of The Guardians of the Galaxy?",
        "option1" : "Yondu Udonta",
        "option2" : "Stakar",
        "option3" : "Gamora",
        "answer" : "Star-Lord"
    },
    14 : {
        "category" : "Medium",
        "question" : "Which Guardian of the Galaxy has the soul stone?",
        "option1" : "Vision",
        "option2" : "Thanos",
        "option3" : "Gamora",
        "answer" : "Adam Warlock"
    },
    15 : {
        "category" : "Medium",
        "question" : "What is the name of Deadpool?",
        "option1" : "Slade Wilson",
        "option2" : "Wade Richards",
        "option3" : "Will Storm",
        "answer" : "Wade Wilson"
    },
    16 : {
        "category" : "Medium",
        "question" : "What is the name of the Scarlet Witch?",
        "option1" : "Agatha Harkness",
        "option2" : "Natasha Romanoff",
        "option3" : "Illyana Nikolievna Rasputina",
        "answer" : "Wanda Maximoff"
    },
    17 : {
        "category" : "Medium",
        "question" : "Who carries the eye of agamotto?",
        "option1" : "Agamotto",
        "option2" : "Dormammu",
        "option3" : "Kaecilius",
        "answer" : "Doctor Strange"
    },
    18 : {
        "category" : "Medium",
        "question" : "Which X-Men has the Phoenix Force?",
        "option1" : "Professor X",
        "option2" : "Emma Frost",
        "option3" : "Rogue",
        "answer" : "Jean Grey"
    },
    19 : {
        "category" : "Hard",
        "question" : "Who possess the power of Thor?",
        "option1" : "Thor",
        "option2" : "Odín",
        "option3" : "Beta Ray Bill",
        "answer" : "Whoever who 'holds' his hammer"
    },
    20 : {
        "category" : "Hard",
        "question" : "Who created the infinity stones?",
        "option1" : "One Above All",
        "option2" : "The Living Tribunal",
        "option3" : "The First Firmament",
        "answer" : "Nemesis"
    },
    21 : {
        "category" : "Hard",
        "question" : "What's the name of the son of Mr. Fantastic and the Invisible Woman?",
        "option1" : "Ben Richards",
        "option2" : "Frankie Storm",
        "option3" : "Jonathan Storm",
        "answer" : "Franklin Richards"
    },
    22 : {
        "category" : "Hard",
        "question" : "What's the name of the seventh infinity stone?",
        "option1" : "Mayhem gem",
        "option2" : "Dream gem",
        "option3" : "Omniscience gem",
        "answer" : "Ego gem"
    },
    23 : {
        "category" : "Hard",
        "question" : "What's the real name of the reality stone?",
        "option1" : "Chaos stone",
        "option2" : "Ether",
        "option3" : "Cosmos stone",
        "answer" : "Aether"
    },
    24 : {
        "category" : "Hard",
        "question" : "Which X-men is Juggernaut related to?",
        "option1" : "Colossus",
        "option2" : "Beast",
        "option3" : "Cyclops",
        "answer" : "Professor X"
    },
    25 : {
        "category" : "Very Hard",
        "question" : "The Flerkens are an extremely rare alien race that looks like ...?",
        "option1" : "any form they wish",
        "option2" : "Reptiles",
        "option3" : "Ducks",
        "answer" : "Cats"
    },
    26 : {
        "category" : "Very Hard",
        "question" : "What's the name of the leader of The Celestials?",
        "option1" : "The Living Tribunal",
        "option2" : "Gamiel",
        "option3" : "Arishem",
        "answer" : "One Above All"
    },
    27 : {
        "category" : "Very Hard",
        "question" : "What's the name of the Watcher assigned to observe the Earth?",
        "option1" : "Acba",
        "option2" : "Emnu",
        "option3" : "Ualu",
        "answer" : "Uatu"
    },
    28 : {
        "category" : "Very Hard",
        "question" : "Who killed The Living Tribunal?",
        "option1" : "Death",
        "option2" : "Master Order",
        "option3" : "Lord Chaos",
        "answer" : "The Beyonders"
    },
    29 : {
        "category" : "Very Hard",
        "question" : "The Venom Symbiote is a member of an alien race called the ...?",
        "option1" : "Badoon",
        "option2" : "Shi'ar",
        "option3" : "Brood",
        "answer" : "Klyntar"
    },
    30 : {
        "category" : "Very Hard",
        "question" : "Gladiator, Smasher, and Fang are members of what team?",
        "option1" : "Annihilators",
        "option2" : "The Warbound",
        "option3" : "Alpha Flight",
        "answer" : "Shi'ar Imperial Guard"
    }
}
